<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sun Kid</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sun Kid</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anime, Animation, and Modern Media</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Elliot, also known online as Thoskowski may or may not be a trust-fund baby, may or may not be a successful crypto investor, may or may not be living in his mother&amp;rsquo;s basement. Elliot was a gifted child (validated by Stanford-Binet), and he was always aware of it. We can speculate that at some point he was a passionate left-wing liberal arts student, or, at the very least, that he went through an intense phase. He was probably one of the best students of his class. If you spend enough time in the anonymous parts of the internet, at some point you will come across an Elliot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On self-definition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I played with sentences, trying to create my own brand of non-fiction that would make sense for a blog (the majority of the non-fiction that I have written in my life has been journal entries), I circled back to a familiar question: “What do I wish existed?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem is that this question usually does not come with overtly constraining parameters. For example, when I think to myself what book, or software I wish existed, parameters are essentially irrelevant. When applying this to my own life, it does not make sense to ask myself ‘what person do I wish existed.” I have to define myself in the context of given parameters: my upbringing, my familial story, etc. When framed like this, the question becomes much harder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
